Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 7: Library departments and services, 1959-2008
  - Subseries 7.3: Collection development, 1964-2001
    - Collection management, 1991-1995 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Collection management services statistical report, 2003-2004 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Disposed of library materials, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Document acquisitions department, 1990-1996 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Duplicate books, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - "Formula-based subject allocation: a practical approach" article, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Government Documents, 1980-1991 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Guidelines for the formulation of collection development policies, 1977 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Library collections management and space use strategies, 1998 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - The video catalog, 1989-1990 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Video and film catalog in Fenwick library media services, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Media center video list, 1994-1995 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Volumes, microforms added to collection, 1966-1972 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Want lists (books for library), 1964 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 7.4: Periodicals, 1963-1996
    Contains information on the periodicals collection.
    - Index weeding project, 1995 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Journals withdrawal list, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Missing issues (Journals), 1995 (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Periodicals, management by objective (MBO), 1979 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Periodicals holding list, subject list, 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Periodicals listing of GMU library, 1963 May-1974 January (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Periodicals and serials holding list, 1984 September (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Periodicals and serials holding list, 1985 March (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1987 September (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1989 March (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1990 January (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1992 October (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1992 January (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Periodicals holdings list, 1994 June (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Periodicals on disc journals list, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Periodical standing, 1994-1996 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Periodicals, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Periodicals, 1994-1995 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Serials, 1990-1995 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Serials sharing project, 1988-1992 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Virginia union list, 1980-1981 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Water environment federation agreement, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 7.5: Reference, 1976-2000
    Contains information on the reference department.
    - Computers in libraries conference, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Core reference sources in science and technology, 1999 April (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Cost analysis of reference department activities, 1986 July-October (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - English 302 library instruction, 1988 August (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Information desk plans, 1995 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Information desk, 1982-1994 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      Service results and thanks, budget, questions, requests, meeting minutes
    - Management by objective (MBO), reference, 1979-1980 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Memorandum to reference staff, 1987 August 10 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Nursing journal information, 1983-1985 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Online searching services, 1987-1989 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Program review of reference department, 1988 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Program review of reference department, 1989 January (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Proposal for a pilot program for end user drop in online searching, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Psychology research information, 1982-1988 (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Reference annex, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Reference department, 1988-1992 (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Reference department, 1984-2000 (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Reference department files, 1989, 1999 (Box 155, Folder 22)
      Checkout file, handout index, empty forms
    - Reference department network, undated (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Reference desk services policy, ready reference packet, 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Reference office, 1991-1992 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Reference office, 1992-1995 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Reference policies and procedures manual, 1980 January (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Reference policies and procedures manual, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Reference policies and procedures manual, 1989, 1993 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Reference policies and procedures manual, 1993 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Reference service, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Reference service core competencies training program, 2002 September 4 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Research guide for nursing, 1985-1989 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Research help, undated (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Statistical research services, 1999 August 1 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      Resources to be available in Fenwick library, room C103
    - Summer session, 1987-1988 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Superterminal, network terminal, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Team training for electronic products, undated (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - U-Search, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 7.6: Other services, 1969-2008
    Includes material relating to other services the library provides such as workshops and seminars, readings and events, library instruction and resources.
    - A directory of library resources in Northern Virginia, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Academic microcomputers, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Advanced internet training at Johnson center library, undated (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Affirmative action bibliography, 1995 (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Computer science education department program, 1988 (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Computerization of the library, 1969 (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Computerized career guidance, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Corporate research service program (CRSP), fee-based services at Arlington Campus Library, 1998-2001 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Educational offerings, 2008 (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Fenwick fellows, 2001 March 12 (Box 156, Folder 23)
      Email about applying to the program
    - Graduate and faculty seminars, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Graduate orientation, 1995 Fall (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Graduate programs, 1988 (Box 156, Folder 26)
    - Handicapped and disabled access and Kurzwell reading machine, 1981-1984 (Box 156, Folder 27)
    - Internet literacy (Hans Bergman), 1995 (Box 156, Folder 28)
    - The library and the humanities seminar, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Library instruction consortium flyer, undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Library instruction and use, 1976-1982 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Library media services, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Library print services, 1994 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Library resources for new graduate programs, 1988-1992 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Library services for education department students and faculty, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Microcomputers library (file in Dr. Siff's folder), 1989 October 30 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Minority affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Minority student services, 1985-1993 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous services and pamphlets, 1961-2004 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      Collection access division, public services, VIVA, Special Collections, annual report
    - New faculty orientation, 1988-1994 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Open access information packet, 2008 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Open source course reserve (OSCR) GMUtant software, 1999-2000 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Orientation, 1983-1986 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Orientation new faculty, 1996 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Printouts of online GMU library links, 2001 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Programs and services packet, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Proposal for an English 101 library skills workbook, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Reading, 1978 May (Box 158, Folder 4)
      James Dickey poetry reading
    - Reading, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
      Peter Klappert reading
    - Reading, 1978 March (Box 158, Folder 6)
      Student poetry reading
    - Relationship between Krasnow Institute library and GMU library system, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Scholars center, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Service guide, faculty services, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Service priviledges by patron type, 1995 Spring-Summer (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Services for distance learners (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Serving Northern Virginia, services, resources, schedule of fees, undated (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Sociology and anthropology library collection, 1986 December 11 (Box 158, Folder 13)
      Report
    - Teaching and learning information competencies: models, programs and future directions, 1998 November 19 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Undergraduate library, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Urban systems engineer, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Webpage development for novices, 1999 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Workshops and seminars, A place for all seasons: the library and the humanities, 1979 September (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Workshops and seminars, Centennial celebrations: Anna Eleanor Roosevelt, 1984 October (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Workshops and seminars, conference on teaching and writing poetry and fiction, undated (Box 158, Folder 20)
      Photograph
    - Workshops and seminars, Gunston Hall, 1978 October-1979 February (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - Workshops and seminars, Reference librarians information exchange, 1977 July 18 (Box 158, Folder 22)
      Cassette tape
    - Workshops and seminars, resource identification workshop, 1979 March (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - Workshops and seminars, special activities, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 24)
    - Workshops and seminars, Vietnamese student club, 1979-1980 (Box 158, Folder 25)
    - Workshops and seminars, Workshops and seminars held at Special Collections and research center for the Federal Theatre Project, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 26)
    - Workshops and seminars, writers club, undated (Box 158, Folder 27)
      Three photographs
  - Subseries 7.7: Exhibits, 1955-2007
    Contains photographs, brochures, publicity, and display materials for exhibits created by and displayed at Fenwick Library. More exhibit material can be found in Series 11 oversize material.
    - 7 collections from SC&A, 1986 Spring-Summer (Box 158, Folder 28)
    - 15th anniversary, 1987 April-1988 January (Box 158, Folder 29)
    - 19th and 20th century collections, 2001 (Box 158, Folder 30)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, 4 year status, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 31)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, 2001 (Box 158, Folder 32)
      1972 copies
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, Advisory Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 158, Folder 33)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, Citizens Committee on Higher Education in Northern Virginia, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 34)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, Community colleges, 1963, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 35)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, "Connections", Virginia economic bridge initiative, 1991, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 36)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, consideration of sites for GMC, 1950s (Box 158, Folder 37)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 38)
      Correspondence and announcements
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 39)
      Display cards
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, GMU independent status, undated (Box 158, Folder 40)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, Mason Gazette, 2002 January/February (Box 158, Folder 41)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, circa 1978 (Box 158, Folder 42)
      Photographs and negatives of Harper's Weekly army beef crossing Occoquan; Baily's crossroads campus; Fairfax campus; Governor Holton signing GMU Independence
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, publications, Broadside, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 43)
    - 30th anniversary exhibit, Section 15-692.2, Code of Virginia, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 44)
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, catalog, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      Comment book
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      DVD Rom
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, Fairfax campus, 2004 September 30 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - 40th anniversary exhibit, reception, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - 150 years of photography, 1989 July-1990 April (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - circa 2000s (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - African art yesterday and today, 1979 September-October (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Dumas african exhibit, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - African items, 1986 Spring (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - AIPC - four photographs, 1988 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Alexander Haight, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - America's National Theatre in the thirties, 1983 January 29 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - American symphony orchestra league, 1978 October (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - An accurate system of surveying exhibition, 2006 August (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Austin, TX exhibit coordination, 1977 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - Black women exhibit, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - Brown vs. Board of education event, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - Burt Lancaster, 1987 Summer (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - C. Harrison Mann reception, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - C. Harrison Mann, 1979 May 22 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - C. Harrison Mann, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 24)
      Four photographs
    - Celebration of learning, 1998 November 19 (Box 159, Folder 25)
    - Collegial gathering invite for exhibit of journals, 2003 (Box 159, Folder 26)
    - Constitutional exhibit (Governor Baliles visit), 1987 September 17 (Box 159, Folder 27)
    - Contrasts - items from Special Collections and Archives, 1985-1986 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Documents about Virginia documents, circa 2000s (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Drummond collection, 1978 January (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Eighteenth century medicine, 1979 October-November (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Einstein exhibits, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Albert Einstein, 1979 October (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Exhibit comments, 2004 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Exhibit display cases brochure, 1981 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Exhibit labels, circa 1980s (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Exhibit loans, 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Exhibit materials, 2000 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Fall for the book festival, 1999 September 23-25 (Box 160, Folder 12)
      Events newspaper
    - Fall for the book festival, 1999 (Box 160, Folder 13)
      Invitation, program, pamphlet, keepsake
    - Fall for the book festival, 1999 September 23-25 (Box 160, Folder 14)
      Poster, bookmarks, receipts, flyers, program, newspaper
    - Father K, 1980 April 16 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Fenwick free flicks, 1980 Spring (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Fenwick library art gallery, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Flach collection, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Floating ideas of nature, 2002 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Floating ideas of nature, 2002 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - French exhibit, 2007 Spring (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Frost, 2001 (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - Frost, 2001 (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - George Harris, 1979 March (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - GMU documentary history, abstract from first doctoral dissertation Carolyn Kreiter-Kurylo, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - GMU documentary history, annual report, 1960 (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - GMU documentary history, annual report university libraries, 1979-1980 (Box 160, Folder 27)
    - GMU documentary history, arts gala, 1984-1990 (Box 160, Folder 28)
    - GMU documentary history, Barter theatre, 1982-1983 (Box 160, Folder 29)
    - GMU documentary history, Broadside first issue, 1969 October 28 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - GMU documentary history, 1950s-1960s (Box 161, Folder 2)
      Copies of historic materials
    - GMU documentary history, Faculty senate first meeting agenda, members, 1972-1973 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - GMU documentary history, First Phoebe, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - GMU documentary history, GMU General information, 1976-1993 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - GMU documentary history, G. W. Johnson speech, inaugural speech, 1979 April 7 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - GMU documentary history, Gunston ledger first issue, 1963 October 15 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - GMU documentary history, House bill 210 and an act to amend Code of Virginia to create GMU, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - GMU documentary history, Johnson center, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - GMU documentary history, resolution authorizing UVA branch in Northern Virginia, 1955 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - GMU documentary history, Robinson professors biographies, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - GMU documentary history, 1960s-1970s (Box 161, Folder 12)
      Sampling of GMC general brochures
    - GMU documentary history, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 13)
      Souvenir programs, Law school ceremonies
    - GMU documentary history, University seals, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - GMU documentary history, UVA board of visitors, circa 2004 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - GMU now and as it might have been, 1980 January (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - GMU special collections, 1981 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - German war art 1939-1945, 1979 April-May (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Gibbes art gallery, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - Hippolyte Bayard, 1981 November-December (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - International year of the child, 1979 August-December (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - Irish week, 1981 April (Box 161, Folder 22)
    - "It can't happen here", FTP archives B'Nai B'Rith, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 23)
    - Items in the office of the President, 2000 (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - John Duncan exhibit, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - Duncan, John M., 2002 (Box 161, Folder 26)
    - John M. Duncan, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 27)
    - Kennedy center, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 28)
    - Le Voyeur, 1982 March (Box 161, Folder 29)
    - Library exhibits, 1975-1981 (Box 161, Folder 30)
    - Marilyn Mahoney, 1982 February (Box 161, Folder 31)
    - Martin Luther King exhibit, 2004 (Box 161, Folder 32)
    - Mary S. Hammond, Landsouth, 1981 September-October (Box 161, Folder 33)
    - McGraw exhibit, circa 2000s (Box 161, Folder 34)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, appraisal information, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 35)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, authors reception, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 36)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, book sale and book exhibit, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 37)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, bookmark, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 38)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, catalog, 2002 (Box 161, Folder 39)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, catalog preliminary materials, 2003 (Box 161, Folder 40)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, celebration group, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, conservation and volume labeling, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      Draft letter of gift, donations
    - Millionth volume exhibit, exhibition, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Fenwick fellow lectures, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Full Text special issue, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, miscellaneous topics, 2002-2003 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Anna Moffo, circa 2002 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Adrien Matie Legendre, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Antoine Reynauld, 2002-2003 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Aritmetica Prattica, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Arrigo Boito, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Bruno Walter, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Euclid, 2002-2003 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Giacomo Puccini, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Giuseppe DiStefano, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Goursat, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Gustav Mahler, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 21)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Lagrange 1808, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 22)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Lagrange 1888, 1889, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 23)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Luigi Cremona, 2002-2003 (Box 162, Folder 24)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Mstislav Rostropovich, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 25)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Pietro Mascagni, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 26)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on printers, circa 2003 (Box 162, Folder 27)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Robert Simson, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 28)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, research on Rosa Ponselle, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 29)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Struppa additional donations, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 30)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Struppa biographical information, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Struppa books general information, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, Struppa correspondence, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, student essay contest, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Millionth volume exhibit, website, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Milton Barnes, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Molka Reich donation, 1980 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Molka Reich marionettes, 1980 June (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Molka Reich marionettes, 1984 November (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Mosby exhibit, 1979 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - National library week, 1979 April (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - National library week, 1979 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - National women's history exhibit, 1986 March (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - NOVA faculty artists, a continuing show, 1979 February-April (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - NVAH the gray ghost reconjured, 1979 October (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Objects from Africa, 1986 September-1987 March (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Ollie Atkins, 1978 September 15 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Paintings and prints, 1983 March-April (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Parody exhibit, circa 2000s (Box 163, Folder 19)
    - Peoples theatre festival exhibit San Francisco, 1981 September (Box 163, Folder 20)
    - Peterson collection, 1978 August (Box 163, Folder 21)
    - Proposed exhibits, 1980-1982 (Box 163, Folder 22)
    - Queens museum, 1980 (Box 163, Folder 23)
    - Qotbi activities, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 24)
    - Recent acquisitions, circa 2000s (Box 163, Folder 25)
    - Recent acquisitions, fine printing, circa 2000s (Box 163, Folder 26)
    - Reception for alumni and friends, 2005 October 20 (Box 163, Folder 27)
    - Reston 30th birthday, 1994 May 4 (Box 163, Folder 28)
    - Simplicity, permanence and economy, 2004 (Box 163, Folder 29)
    - Sizemore exhibit, 1980 (Box 163, Folder 30)
    - Chris Sizemore exhibit guests, 1980 March 25-April 15 (Box 163, Folder 31)
    - The paintings of Eve (Chris Sizemore), 1980 March-April (Box 163, Folder 32)
    - Smith college Hallie Flanagan and the Federal Theatre Project, 1975-1982 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Smithsonian traveling exhibit, 1981-1982 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Statue of liberty, 1986 Summer (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Stowe, 2001 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Uncle Tom's cabin display, circa 2001 (Box 164, Folder 5)